MBULELO PANI

ABOUT ME

I am a Junior Web Developer, based in Cape Town. I have experience in building, testing and maintaining full stack websites. I also have experience working independently as well as working within a team, and I love to learn on the go. My passion is designing the functionality of neat and interactive websites.

PERSON DETAILS

Full name - Mbulelo Pani

Sex - Male

Date of Birth - 29/08/1997

Region - Cape Town, Western Cape
Nationality - South African

Email - mbulelopani09@gmail.com

Phone - +27 703 6422

Web profile - mbulelopani.herokuapp.com

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2021 - Feb, 2022 - Oviond

Web Developer Intern

 Built integration API's to handle data reports from apps such as YouTube, Facebook.

Apr - July, 2021 - TouchFoundry

Web Developer Intern

- Designed website elements such as navbars, buttons and animations.
- Performed simple user experience testing on websites.

Nov - Apr, 2021 - LC Studio

Web Developer Intern

- Built code to connect databases such as MongoDB with client side websites.
- Did code cleaning removing unnecessary lines and spaces.

Oct 2019 - Jan 2020 - Sage Futuremakers Foundation

Assistant Facilitator (part-time)

- Assist facilitators in tutoring programming to high schoolers
- Plan lessons
- Assist in recruiting potential students from the townships

EDUCATION

Feb- Aug, 2020 - Lifechoices Academy

Course: Fullstack Web Development

June - Nov, 2019 - Melisizwe Computer Lab Project

Course: Intro to Programming Certificate: Systems Development

2016 - Dec, 2018 - Northlink College

Course: Electrical Engineering

Certificate: N4

2011 - 2015 - Sizimisele Technical High School

Course: Electrical Engineering

Certificate: Matric

SKILLS

Frontend design

HTML CSS Javascript Boostrap 4

Python

Mobile responsiveness

Frameworks

NodeJS React VueJS MongoDB

Soft Skills

Teamwork Accountability Open-mindedness Critical thinking Time management

ACTIVITIES

Interests

Database design Machine learning Software design Robotics Hobbies

Reading Meditation Circuit building Gaming

REFERENCES

Khanya Qongqo

NGO: Harare CAN Foundation
Position: Marketer/manager

Contact: Qongqokhanya@gmail.com

Gift Khangamwa

NGO: SageFuturemakersFoundation

Position: Facilitator

Contact: Gift@melisizwe.co.za